californiapsychics.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy Policy | California Psychics

June 7, 2018 

Outlook Amusements, Inc. ("Outlook") values your trust and is committed to the responsible management, use and protection of your information. This Privacy Policy describes the types of information Outlook collects from and about you when you visit our Web site, [www.californiapsychics.com](https://www.californiapsychics.com/) and our applications (collectively, the "Sites"), and explains how Outlook may use and disclose such information, as well as your ability to control certain uses of it. Please take the time to read and understand this policy. 

If you have questions regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [Privacy@californiapsychics.com](mailto:privacy@californiapsychics.com)

FOR ENTERTAINMENT ONLY 

THIS SERVICE IS FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY. YOU MUST BE EIGHTEEN YEARS OF AGE OR OLDER TO USE THE PREMIUM AREAS OF THIS SERVICE. ALL PURCHASES USING CREDIT CARDS, DEBIT CARDS, PAYPAL ACCOUNT, OR OTHER PAYMENT MECHANISM SHALL ONLY BE MADE BY THE CARD OR ACCOUNT HOLDER. WE WANT YOU TO ENJOY AND BENEFIT FROM YOUR READING, AND OUR PSYCHICS MAKE EVERY EFFORT TO PROVIDE YOU WITH HELPFUL ADVICE. HOWEVER, THIS INFORMATION SHOULD NOT BE USED IN PLACE OF ANY RECOMMENDATIONS BY MEDICAL, LEGAL, OR FINANCIAL PROFESSIONALS OR OTHER PROFESSIONAL COUNSELORS. IT IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY TO EVALUATE ANY INFORMATION, OPINION, ADVICE OR OTHER CONTENT AVAILABLE THROUGH OUR SITES. 

Quick Guide to Contents: 

  1. Information We Collect
  2. How We Use the Information
  3. How We Share Your Information
  4. Your Rights and Choices
  5. Retention of Your Data
  6. International Transfers
  7. How We Secure Your Information
  8. Testimonials
  9. Third Party Content, Links, and Plug-ins
  10. Send to a Friend
  11. Children's Privacy
  12. Revisions to this Privacy Policy
  13. How to Contact Us

1\. Information We Collect. 

There are several ways we may obtain information about you, including through (A) information you provide to us directly; and (B) information that we automatically collect. This includes data that identifies you personally whether directly (e.g., your name) or indirectly (e.g., information about your online use). 

Information You Provide 

Outlook collects personal information from you when you choose to share it with us. This may include when you create an online account with us, talk to a psychic, enter contests, participate in surveys, subscribe to a service (like our horoscopes), take quizzes, post to message boards, participate in a chat room, request information from us, or otherwise contact us. The types of personal information that may be collected on these pages include name, address, age, date of birth, gender, e-mail address, telephone number, credit or debit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various services. 

We do not ask for, access, or track any location-based information from your mobile device at any time while downloading or using our mobile services. 

Information Automatically Collected 

As is true of most websites, we may use technologies such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, scripts, log files, or local shared objects (Flash cookies/HTML5), to automatically or passively collect certain information about visitors to our Sites and interactions with our emails and online advertisements, and to allow Outlook to keep track of analytics and certain statistical information which enables Outlook to improve its Sites and provide you with more relevant content and advertising on our Sites and other sites. For information about our use of cookies and other similar technologies through the Sites, you can read our Cookie Policy. 

Please note, we may automatically collect certain non-personal information from you, including, but not limited to, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, unique device identifier of any of your computer(s) or device(s) that are used to access the Sites, and the domain name from which you accessed the Sites. We also may collect information about your use of the Sites, including the date and time you visit the Sites, the areas or pages of the Sites that you visit, the amount of time you spend viewing or using the Sites, the number of times you return to the Sites, other click-stream or site usage data, emails that you open, forward or click-through to our Sites, and other sites that you may visit. 

We partner with third party advertising networks to display advertising on our Sites and to manage our advertising on other sites. Some of our advertising partners, marketing affiliates, or analytics providers may use technology such as cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, log files, or local shared objects (Flash cookies/HTML5) when they advertise on our Sites, which may send these advertisers information including your non-personal information. We do not have access to, or control over, these third parties' use of cookies or other tracking technologies. 

To learn more about your advertising choices relating to the collection and use of your information, please see the Your Rights and Choices section below. 

Combination of Information 

We may combine the information we receive from and about you, including information you provide to us and information we automatically collect through our Sites, as well as information collected from other online sources or from third party sources (including social networks that you use to connect with Outlook) to help us tailor our communications to you and to improve our Sites. 

2\. How We Use the Information. 

Outlook may use the information we collect from and about you for a variety of business purposes, as discussed below. We are committed to protecting and maintaining the privacy of your information. Therefore, we will process your data only in accordance with applicable data protection law and this Privacy Policy. 

We will have a lawful basis for processing your data if: 

  * We need to process your information in order to provide you with the products or service you have requested or to enter into a contract; 
  * You have consented to such processing; 
  * We have a legitimate interest for processing your data – e.g., for fraud prevention; network and information systems security; data analytics; enhancing, modifying or improving our services; identifying usage trends; determining the effectiveness of promotional campaigns; and personalization of the service using data to make it easier and faster for you to place orders; and/or 
  * We are required to do this by law (for example, where it is necessary to retain it in connection with potential litigation). 

Outlook may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: 

  * To provide you with the services that you have requested. For example, if you sign up for horoscopes we will send you horoscopes, or if you have entered a contest and win, we will send you an email notification that you have won. 
  * To respond to your inquiries, fulfill orders, and contact and communicate with you when necessary; 
  * To develop new products or services and to conduct analysis to enhance current products and services; 
  * To review the usage and operations of our Sites and improve the design and content of our Sites; 
  * To personalize your experience on the Sites and provide you with customized content, targeted offers, and advertising on the Sites or via email; 
  * To contact you with information, newsletters, and promotional or other marketing materials offering products or services from Outlook or on behalf of our partners, affiliates, or subsidiaries that we think you may be interested in; 
  * To use your data in an aggregated non-specific format for analytical and demographic purposes (this processing may involve profiling – for example to create audiences based on demographic or location based information for marketing and customization purposes); 
  * To address problems with the Sites or our business; 
  * To manage our telecommunications networks; 
  * To protect the security or integrity of the Sites and our business; 
  * As otherwise described to you at the point of data collection; and 
  * To use and disclose your credit/debit card or payment account information only to process payments and prevent fraud 

Additionally, if you use the Sites to connect with third party services you authorize us to use information from and about you, on your behalf, to interact with these third party services based on your requests. 

3\. How We Share Your Information. 

Sharing of Information by You 

The Sites offer many ways to find, enjoy, and share content. Your activity in connection with the Sites may include filling out surveys, reviewing and rating products or services, inquiring about or using our services, participation in online communities, "liking" or "sharing" our content to your social media accounts or pages or otherwise interacting with the Sites. Any information you may disclose on our Sites, in blogs, on message boards, in chat rooms, or on other public areas on the Sites or other third-party websites, applications, or services that the Sites may link to, becomes public information. Please exercise caution when disclosing personal information in these public areas. 

Sharing of Information by Us 

We will share or disclose the information we collect from and about you with third parties only in the ways that are described in this Privacy Policy. We do not sell your personal information to unaffiliated third parties. We will only share your information in the following ways: 

  * (a) if it is for the purpose(s) for which you provided the information; 
  * (b) with your consent; 
  * (c) as may be required by law or as we think necessary to protect our company, to protect others from injury, or on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law (e.g., in response to a court order or subpoena, in response to a law enforcement agency request, when we believe that someone is causing (or about to cause) injury to or interference with the rights or property of another, or when we believe that someone has violated our Terms and Conditions; 
  * (d) with other persons or companies with whom we contract to carry out business, professional or technical support functions for us (e.g., service providers - see below); and/or 
  * (e) with our affiliated companies, subsidiaries, or divisions.

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy subsidiaries, affiliates, assets, or other business units. If another entity acquires us or any of our assets, information we have collected about you may be transferred to such entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. Should such a sale or transfer occur, we will use reasonable efforts to try to require that the transferee use personal information provided through the Sites in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. 

Outlook may also share aggregate or anonymous non-personal information with third parties, including affiliated companies and non-affiliated companies, for their marketing or analytics uses. 

Sharing with Service Providers 

Our operations and maintenance contractors sometimes have limited access to your information in the course of providing products or services to Outlook. These contractors include vendors and suppliers that provide us various products and services, including, but not limited to, credit card processing, e-mail distribution technology, live operator services, and/or content for the operation and maintenance of our Sites. Access to your information by these contractors is limited to the information reasonably necessary for the contractor to perform its limited function for Outlook. We also contractually require that our operations and maintenance contractors (1) protect the privacy of your personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy, and (2) not use or disclose your personal information for any purpose other than providing us with products and services, except as required by law. 

Our Psychics/Your Privacy 

Note that our psychics are independent contractors and not employed directly by Outlook. We contractually require that our psychics protect the privacy of your personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy and not use or disclose your personal information for any purpose other than providing you with the services you request through the Sites or by phone. You should also take care to protect your personal information and privacy. There is no reason that you should provide any of our psychics with personal contact information, specific financial information, including, but not limited to, account numbers or other confidential information related to your identity. It is a violation of our Terms and Conditions for you to be in direct contact with any of our psychics outside the service – if you do so, Outlook bears no liability for any resulting actions, and your ability to use our services may be revoked. 

4\. Your Rights and Choices. 

We respect your privacy rights and provide you with reasonable access and rights to the personal data that you may have provided through your use of the Sites. If you wish to make changes to your account information, you can do so by accessing the My Account section of your member account or by sending an e-mail with your requests to [Privacy@californiapsychics.com](mailto:privacy@californiapsychics.com). If you live in the European Economic Area (EEA), and wish to access, amend, delete, or transfer any personal data we hold about you, you may send an e-mail with your requests to [Privacy@californiapsychics.com](mailto:privacy@californiapsychics.com), or contact us by postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will make every effort to respond to your request within 30 days. To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or fulfilling your requests. 

Please note that while any changes you make will be reflected in active user databases instantly or within a reasonable period of time, we may retain all information you submit for backups, archiving, prevention of fraud and abuse, analytics, satisfaction of legal obligations, or where we otherwise reasonably believe that we have a legitimate reason to do so. 

In certain circumstances, you also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information by us. You may decline to share certain personal data with us, in which case we may not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality of the Sites or certain of our services. In circumstances where you have provided your consent, you also have the right to withdraw your consent. 

If you believe your right to privacy granted by applicable data protection laws has been infringed upon, please contact [Privacy@californiapsychics.com](mailto:privacy@californiapsychics.com). If you live in the EEA, you also have a right to lodge a complaint with data protection authorities. 

Opt Out Preferences 

You can view or change your preferences to receive subscriptions (e.g., horoscopes, newsletters), promotional communications, and alerts at any time by accessing the Mail Preferences and My Alerts sections of your member account, or by contacting us at [Privacy@californiapsychics.com](mailto:privacy@californiapsychics.com). You also may choose to stop receiving such communications delivered by e-mail by following the unsubscribe instructions included in the emails. 

Tracking Options and California Do Not Track Disclosures 

Certain parts of our Sites require cookies. You are free to set your browser or operating system settings to limit certain tracking or to decline cookies, but by doing so, you may not be able to use certain features on the Sites or take full advantage of all of our offerings. Please refer to your Web browser's or operating system's website or "Help" section for more information on how to delete and/or disable your browser or operating system from receiving cookies or controlling your tracking preferences. 

Our system may not respond to Do Not Track requests or headers from some or all browsers. To learn more about the use of cookies or other technologies to deliver more relevant advertising and to know your choices about not having this information used by certain service providers, please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies, please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html). Please note that you may not be able to opt out of being served targeted advertising from certain ad networks, and you also will continue to receive generic ads. 

YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS 

Outlook collects various types of personal information about you, both online and offline, during the course of our business relationship. Under California law, if you are a resident of California, you may make a written request to Outlook for information about how we have shared your personal information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the prior calendar year, as well as a list of categories of information shared. For purposes of this California Privacy Rights notice, third parties include companies within our "family" of companies, such as those companies we own, that own us, or under common control with us. To make such a request, please send an email to [Privacy@californiapsychics.com](mailto:privacy@californiapsychics.com). 

California customers may request further information about our compliance with this law by e-mailing [Privacy@californiapsychics.com](mailto:privacy@californiapsychics.com). Please note that we are only required to respond to one request per customer each year, and we are not required to respond to requests made by means other than through this e-mail address. 

5\. Retention of Your Data 

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to address outstanding account balances, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

6\. International Transfers 

Outlook is a global business and it, or its service providers, may process, transfer, and store information about our users on servers located in a number of countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA), including in the United States. Since we are committed to protecting your information, we take steps to ensure that there are appropriate safeguards in place when we transfer that data. 

7\. How We Secure Your Information 

Outlook is committed to handling your customer information with high standards of information security. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations and generally accepted standards to guard your nonpublic personal information, both during transmission and once we receive it. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Sites, you can contact us at [Privacy@californiapsychics.com](mailto:privacy@californiapsychics.com). 

8\. Testimonials 

We display personal testimonials of customers on our Sites in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [Privacy@californiapsychics.com](mailto:privacy@californiapsychics.com). 

9\. Third Party Content, Links, and Plug-ins 

Our Sites include links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Outlook. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We are not responsible for the practices of such sites, and encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit. 

The Sites may offer you the ability to interact with social plugins from social media sites, such as the Facebook Like and Share buttons, and other widgets and interactive mini-programs that run on our Sites. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Sites. As with linked sites, we have no control over the information that is collected, stored, or used by social network plugins, and are not responsible for the practices of such sites. In addition, we may receive certain information about you from a third party social network if you choose to link to us or use certain social media features, based on your registration and privacy settings on those third party services. 

10\. Send to a Friend 

If you choose to use our referral function to tell a friend about our Sites, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the Sites. Outlook stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [Privacy@californiapsychics.com](mailto:privacy@californiapsychics.com) to request that we remove this information from our database. 

11\. Children's Privacy 

Protecting children's privacy is important to us. Our Sites are not intended for use by anyone under the age of 16. Outlook does not knowingly collect or store personal information from anyone under the age of 16. Premium services may not be used by anyone under the age of 18. If you have concerns about our Sites or the services offered on our Sites, or if you believe that your child under 16 has gained access to our Sites, you may contact us at [Privacy@californiapsychics.com](mailto:privacy@californiapsychics.com). 

12\. Revisions to this Privacy Policy 

Outlook reserves the right, at our sole discretion, to change, modify, add, remove, or otherwise revise portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will post the change(s) on the Sites. Your continued use of the Sites following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. If we change the Privacy Statement in a material way, we will provide appropriate notice to you. 

13\. How to Contact Us. 

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, you may e-mail us at [Privacy@californiapsychics.com](mailto:privacy@californiapsychics.com) or write to us at the following address: 

Privacy  
2900 W. Alameda, Suite 400   
Burbank, CA 91505
